Thank you for watching.
And now, it's time for Nogizaka Kensetsu Chūchū, hosted by Bananaman, so please welcome.
This is our newbie, Nogizaka-chan.
No, no, no, no, no.
Let's go, let's go, let's go!
Ready?
Here we go.
Now then, please announce today's project.
Let's go! I'm here with Mari Mito, the secret carpenter.
Hi!
Tonight, the students from the 3rd to 5th terms will be going head-to-head, breaking down the barriers between the older and younger generations.
The new generation of Nogizaka will aim for even greater heights through friendly competition.
So this time... we're going to divide you into two groups.
We're going to have them kill each other.
It's a game called "Killing each other".
I haven't seen you in a jersey for a long time.
I miss it.
It's like you only wear jerseys at certain times.
I don't know if it's another story or not, but Nogizaka-san never told me.
I know I always say this, but don't be shy with your senpai.
And senpai have their own feelings.
The fourth term is the best, so you have to do both.
There are many aspects to being a senior and many aspects to being a junior.
But it doesn't matter today.
But it's kind of a physical battle.Well, it's kind of a physical challenge, isn't it?
I'm at the peak of my maturity, so I'm a little nervous about that, to be honest.
But I'm only 21.
Lilia and I are 20, too, and not much has changed.
There are third-term students like that.
While Yoda is talking about Ume...
It's Schuber.
I'm not very strong, but I've got the energy.
And now the fourth term...
Are they strong?
Yes, we're strong... because we're united.
We're united... in more ways than one.
Yes, it's strong.
The 4th term is united for some reason.
Shibata, the RPG at the bowling game last time was fun.
I'm not funny myself when I saw it.
It was funny even when I saw it myself
He's just an uncle.
He's a super uncle.
You can't lose to Semiah and the others in the athletic world.
I'm having so much fun.
What's going on?
It's just... It's like a gymnastics day.
It's a gymnastics festival.
It's like... well, you know...I've already done this, so I'm just going to do what I have to do to win.
By doing our best to win the hearts of the people
By doing our best, we will strengthen the bond of Nogizaka as a whole.
I don't mean that we're bickering.
And what about the 5th term?
They think the 5th term will definitely lose.
So, Imagami will definitely ask the 5th term to do their best here.
Year by year.
What do you think of the 5th term?
But they're the freshest.
You said it so clearly.
We're fresh in a way that the seniors aren't.
But for us...
What we have more than our seniors.
Freshness.
That's true.
You can't do that with Nakanishi.
But the 5th term students have each other.
We're not good at sports.
But they can compensate for each other.
Nakanishi might be a drag.
Sorry... sorry... sorry... sorry...
All 5th term students.
You're going with the Unity kids.
Ogawa's already the shortest but he'll be fine.Ogawa is already the shortest, but he's okay.
But bowling qualifiers are the best!
At the snack bowling tournament.
That's right.
Fifth graders still protecting Umezawa-san.
But I still didn't get to show my best side.
Oh, he's not wearing his gold jersey today.
It's back to normal.
You've changed a lot since then, haven't you?
We've all grown since then.
Just for today...
I'm going to work hard without hesitation.
I wonder if any of them will get mad at me.
There might be some.
Behind the scenes... you... you...
Once when you were moony.
Don't worry, we don't have a black body.
Why isn't he here?
I wish Kuromi was here today.
I'm looking forward to it.
It's a battle of pride.
We don't have the merchandise.
Hey, that's not what the semis are for.
You don't want the merchandise.You don't need a product.
Three is the coolest.
First game goes between three
Tug of war
The program's favorite three-team tug-of-war simultaneously.
Each team must place a marker at the top of the rope.
out of the line of their own team to win.
The first round is for two players each.
How about the third round? Do you have a strategy?
Well, we're going to win.
We're going to win.
I don't have anything to say.
Well, if you don't win this one, the score will be too close to call.
Will there be a fourth term, strategy-wise?
Of course.
But look at the members.
Ume-san seems a little strong.
The other three...
They make fun of me.
You don't strike me as the power type.
I'm a power person.
I thought you were flexible.
I can be both.
And Alfie.
Alfie, too.Alfie's is one of them.
How's the fifth term going? It looks a little strong.
Sakura seems confident.
When I was in elementary school, we had a class tug of war.
The teacher had a pretty good plan.
Tug of war isn't always about strength.
The tug of war in the three forests is always a very serious game.
Which tree will win?
And Himuro-san is executed.
Tamura is in full view!
Now then, let's go to Himuro-san's cue!
Kiai de yokara ok!
On Himuro-san's cue, let's get started.
Let's get to it.
Three Forest Tug of War!
Get ready!
Let's start!
Whoa!
Three-key strong!
Ow, ow, ow!
That's it!
That's great!
It's in seconds!
The 3-key player showed overwhelming pull right from the start.
No other team was able to catch them.No other team was able to get by at all.
Ketchik in the shortest time ever.
This was a little bit too strong, wasn't it?
I don't know, I don't know, they didn't really give it their all.
It didn't feel like a victory.
That's Karate Girl!
Karate girl is very strong!
In the second round, we'll face off with the members from here.
We'll face each other in the second round, but we'll do it first round.
There's no side in the strategy meeting.
I'm not sure about the 3-key, but the two who won earlier gave me some advice.
I wonder if Sakaguchi is strong.
But he's been kickboxing lately.
Seriously?
Can I ask you to hit Yoda?
No, no, no.
You kickbox?
So I'm trying to work on my strength.
Instantaneous force might be nice.
And the 4 keys look really strong.
Tamura was giving great advice.
I didn't think so.
What is it now?
I think the teamwork is really good.
I'm sure we'll do well.I'm sure it'll work.
Masami looks strong.
I don't want to lose.
I don't want to lose this kind of thing.
I'm so frustrated.
I was just watching, but I'm so frustrated.
Well, now...
I was just watching and I lost
I'm so frustrated that I'm losing my mind
But you can do it now
I'll do my best.
Oh, well...
I feel like crying
It's okay to do your best
Well, maybe it's just that...
How's the power
But bowling qualifiers are the best
At the parent-child bowling tournament.
Above the sun...
But since you gave me some advice earlier...
5-key was not good at all, but the advice
How will the other two pairs stand up to the 4-key led by Masami, the woman who means more than anyone else?
How will the other two groups stand up to her?
It's only 3 keys, but it's nice.
Are you listening? Everyone!Are you listening? Hey, guys.
I'm listening.
Mr. Himura.
Look at Mr. Himura, please.
Mr. Himura, he's doing the "put it down" pose.
Here we go.
Good luck.
Okay, then.
Tug of war between the three!
Let's start!
Even
Even.
A little pull.
Yoda's down.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
That was a good fight.
You did it, Masami.
Good fight.
Yoda fell in the middle of the fight.
I'm happy for you.
You had a plan?You had a plan.
Just sit back.
If you pull back, you'll lose.
So you timed the effort to the right moment?
Because I have the image of you pulling away at the end.
Next game, Mr. Himura, please.
Hanging Karaoke
Good!
It's good!
Each team is challenged by two people.
The rule is that you can only sing karaoke while one of you is hanging.
The rule is that one person can only sing karaoke while the other is hanging.
Click here to see the members who entered this battle.
The karaoke festival will be reflected in the team's score as it is here!
So, of course, you have to be good at karaoke.
And if you don't sing, it simply won't be reflected in your score.
The first place after the rock-paper-scissors contest went to the third-semester student team!
The theme song was
Synchronicity
Synchronicity.
Really? Then it might be difficult to find the right time to change.
It's a little difficult.
When is it okay to sing, Mr. Himura?
Can I? If I cheat, he'll use this stick and snap it here.
No, no, no, no.No, no, no, no, no.
Shall we go?
Let's get ready for hanging karaoke!
I'm so nervous.
I'm nervous.
I'm getting nervous even though I'm not going to do it.
Oh, no.
Sad to meet you, I'm all alone
I just walk down my street
With my back rounded and my head down, I'm not going anywhere...
I wander in the midst of conflict
I hear you.
I'm the one you pass by at the water's edge
I don't need to know what's going on
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Don't lose your footing.
Okay, you're doing pretty good.
Wow.
That's fun.
It's fun.
Oh, my God.
If you put it on...
It's amazing.Wow.
Wow.
Hang in there.
The 3rd term students with the strategy of hanging on to the foggy good part of the stage.
Minimizing the loss of songs as they move into the second half of the show
Ohadakunana iukunoya
Wow!
Even if you fall, this one too
Slip and fall
Wah
Down, down, down, down
Wow.
Come on!
not yet not yet not yet not yet not yet not yet not yet not yet not yet not yet not yet not yet not yet not yet not yet not yet
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
I can't do it.
I can't do it anymore.
Not yet.
I can't!
Not yet!
Not yet.
Not yet?
This is the part where you throw it away.You've got to get rid of this place.
What's with the throwaway part?
The final showdown.
You know what?
Decide on the last part.
You decide.
There's more.
Wow.
I cried outside.
Oh, no!
Oh, there it is, there it is.
You sang a lot.
Wow, that's great.
But you sang a lot.
Almost. Almost.
Will they be able to do it?
The next song for the two 5th term students was
Influencer
I wonder if there is a pause between "Influencer" and "Influencer"?
It's a few seconds long.
Okuda is quite confident
When I was little, I used to hang on to driveWhen I was a little girl, I used to hang out to drive.
Because if one can do it forever, this one wins.
That's the best way to do it.
The one person who actually sings through the whole thing.
That's what Uncle Driving says.
It's best if one person sings the whole song.
Let's go to the 5th period.
Let the hanging karaoke preparation begin!
drowning
Liverpool
rar
Always looking around at me before I know it
It's good, it's good, it's good
Isn't it fast?
Oh, I've changed
rose, rose, rose
Yes, that's good. Let's get the judges right.
It's still slippery. It's very slippery. Very slippery.
I'm falling. I'm falling.
I think I'd like to take a little picture of this.
You can change the details.
It's a mess.
Yes, no.
Not yet, not yet.Not yet. Not yet.
OK.
That's interesting.
It's interesting.
Nakanishi, who couldn't hang on after that anyway.
Okuda's hand slips
Without being able to make the best use of his excessive strength
without being able to make the most of his excess strength.
You'd better put that on.
You should put on the microphone.
I'd better put on the microphone.
Pockets in my pockets
I danced.
Like time and sun
Light and shadow
Like time and the sun
Coming around
I didn't sing as a baby.
I'm not singing as a baby.
I'm really scared.
And finally, I'll let Nakanishi concentrate on singing, but
I exceeded the limit of six steps
too much.
Oh no!
Oh no!Oh, man.
Nice.
Oh, man.
Done.
I worked hard on this one, though.
This is harder than you can imagine, Mr. Himura.
I was a sweaty mess.
I've been doing this all day.
Something amazing is going to happen later.
The final piece for Yumiki Natsuki...
When I came to my senses
Kataoka
That's right!
How confident are you Yumiki?
My grandma is in this driving
I've been hanging on for decades
To drive.
You know, that health and fitness equipment.
Hanging apparatus.
I'd like to carry on the legacy and do my best.
You're on your own.
No, I'm not.
I did.
I'm probably the worst at hanging on in this world
I'm probably the worst at hanging on.I'm the worst at hanging on.
So what about this one?
If I go to the limit.
I'm going to ruin the second half of the show, and I'm going to go public.
You have 4 minutes 23 seconds.
Four minutes and 23 seconds.
Let's go!
Start preparing for hanging karaoke.
I found myself shoulder to shoulder
I've been thinking about you and before I knew it I liked you
Every time I think of you
I'm kind of sad
Oh, your fingers are gross.
Oh, I see.
That's good. That's good.
I see.
Oh, rest.
That's good.
Mr. Kimura.
I always believed we were meant to be this time.
But somehow, we'd cross paths, and I'd get hurt.
I thought I'd never fall in love.
I've made up my mind to never fall in love.
When he introduced us, you pretended you weren't interested.
And I was.I was.
I couldn't do it anymore.
Not for my birthday, not for Christmas, not for Valentine's Day.
I thought I'd find the strength to spend them all alone.
I'm sure you found it today.
And I'm wondering where you are.
Oh, my God.
You're good.
You're a craftsman.
Craftsmanlike.
Why don't you just tell me why you're doing what you're doing?
Oh, you'll change.
Not yet, not yet.
Okay, okay.
I liked you before I knew it.
Every time I think of you
I can't believe I'm doing something about it.
I realized I had a crush on you
I don't know if I can say it in words
I can't do it, I can't do it, I can't do it
Kaki, I can't take it!
Go, go, go, go!
I like it.
I thought I was supposed to eat this.
I can do it. I can do it.I can do it, I can do it, I can do it.
I was alone and the thought didn't take me away.
Yumi-yumi-yumi-yumi-yumi-yumi-yumi-yum
Yumiki passes the ball to Kaki with a parade step as if he is an experienced player.
Can you keep it up in the second half?
Not yet, not yet!
Yes, it's OK!
He changed his grip.
I wished for love, my heart was open
I knew from the beginning... he was special.
Yes, one can love, even if it's rough.
It's hard to breathe.
I love you so much.
I thought if I really did, I'd disappear.
And then I realized, and then I realized, and then I realized
When I realize I'm in love with you, I'll say I'm in love with you, and then we'll say it to each other.
Not yet, not yet.
Every time I do, I feel sad.
That day is coming.
Ha-ha-ha-ha!
A-ha-ha-ha-ha.
A-ha-ha-ha-ha
A-ha-ha-ha... gone... gone...
It went
Oh, it's funny, it went.Oh, that's interesting.
Yay! - No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
This place is amazing.
The atmosphere is already a hanging artisan.
Thank you very much.
And then you just put it back in the confounding part.
Sweaty danglers.
Like a dancing guard at a construction site.
When you notice...
Scores are announced
The results were announced afterwards
First place
So let's go for it... 1st place!
89 points
Such a high score!
3rd term
Wow!
That's amazing!
Kikumi Shi
I knew you were a top cutter, but you were good.
I didn't think you were such a Kenker.
And now for the second place winner!
Which one is it?
88 points88 points
Mr. Such a Kin
4th term
4th period
Yay, yay, yay!
4th term was good, wasn't it?
Yumiki's hanging craftsman
Good balance.
And now, the third place, the fifth period, with a score of 85.
So-so, so-so.
So, I did my best.
I only got about 4 points.
It was a lot of fun.
But the score difference wasn't that great.
Mai Tamura's first photo book is now on sale!
General sale for the Tokyo leg of the national tour starts on the 12th!
Under Live to be held
Mobile Selection Starts!
Ohitorisama Tengoku" is streaming now!
Hello, this is Nao Yumiki.
Please subscribe to my channel!
So, what I, Nao Yumiki, have been into recently is
painting toys.
I think some of you have toys at home, and some of you don't
some of you have toys at home, and some of you don't.I know some of you don't know that.
Let's paint colorfully with me!
And Yumikinao is addicted to painting toys.
If you are painting toys, you can also paint toys
If you are painting toys